The Overworld.
The biggest sandbox
in the universe is full
of epic tales, millions
and billions of them.
Well guess what?
This one is all mine.
My name is Steve.
And as a child, I yearn for the mines.
It didn't really work out.
So I did a terrible thing.
I grew up.
And just as I expected, it
was a massive bummer.
I really put myself out there,
and it totally blew up in my face.
It was the kind of life that made
a man stare into his potatoes.
And then I remembered I
couldn't give up on my dream.
Not yet.
The lines.
So I bought a pickaxe and a sweet
helmet and this time I was unstoppable.
Turns out my adventure was just beginning.
I'm minding my brains out
until I found two mysterious
artifacts, this thingy,
and that cool thingy.
And when I took those two
thingies together, you guessed it.
It opened a portal to another world.
The overworld.
This place blew my mind.
I'd never seen anything like it.
Whoa!
Turns out it was the place I'd
been looking for my whole life.
A world where anything you
can imagine, you can create.
This is my first house.
My second house?
The third house made
entirely of sheep's wool.
The house.
Life was good.
The only thing missing
was a friend to share it with.
And then this super angry wolf showed up.
So I tamed him with a crusty femur bone.
Yeah.
What?
A boy?
Damn it.
He like a scrunchy scratch on a nutty.
With him by my side, my confidence soared.
Whoo-hoo!
Together, we built endless masterpieces.
The more I built, the better I got.
Dennis, check it out.
Pack up the stand.
Whoa.
Turns out, pandas love to party.
And cows.
Life was perfect.
And the years simply flew by.
Until one day I came
across some strange ruins.
Flint and Steve.
turns out we just opened the
portal to a totally new dimension.
The Nether.
There was no joy or creativity at all.
These piglet broods had
mined this realm into oblivion.
Led by Mt.
Gosha, the evil piglet
sorceress who ruled the place.
Who are you and why are you so proud?
Leave the dog.
Take me instead.
Nothing.
I'll take both of you and that all.
Let's get one thing straight.
Where I come from?
We call this ew.
Malgosha had finally got
what she'd always wanted.
The orb of dominance.
The most powerful cubed-shaped
orb in the entire universe.
Listen up, your pace!
With this soul, I will pillage the
overworld in all, and its goal will be ours!
I couldn't let this happen.
The overworld had saved me,
and now I had to try to save it.
We have to stop our tennis.
So we escaped, and stole back the orb!
That was a sight!
Find him and bring me that orb!
Hurry, Dennis.
Take this to Earth.
Follow my set to 149 Holly Oak Drive.
You got that boy?
Who are the boys?
You're the last health biggest world!
Run!
Up top one!
He ran like the wind.
I didn't know if I'd ever see him
again, but we had a world to save.
So he ran all the way back
to my house on Earth and hit
the most powerful, objective
existence under my water bed.
As long as the orb stays
hidden, the overworld will be safe.
I just pray some doofus doesn't find it.
The late 1980s, Garrett Garrison took
the gaming world by storm, becoming
the undisputed champion of the hit
arcade game, Hunt City Rampage.
His mastery of this two-player
co-op shocked the world.
His effective use of the garbage toss move
earned him the nickname the garbage man.
He became the envy
of the gaming world after
landing a loop in a
six-figure deal with Sisler.
One thing's for sure.
This kid had it all.
You're the garbage man, Garrison?
No autographs.
Have a nice day.
No time has come.
People miss me when I'm gone.
Go, go, miss me when I'm gone.
Go, miss me when I'm gone.
Go, miss me when you're gone.
Go,
I'm a businessman, Darryl, an investor.
Well, I'm about to shuffle some
coal into your choo-choo train.
You're gonna love this next unit.
It's got a water bed.
It's got some pickaxes.
It's got a huge gain from mixed nuts.
It's got an array of
unisex turquoise blouses.
That sounds terrible.
I think it's also got a 1978 Atari Cosmos.
1978 Atari.
Cosmos.
That's what it says here.
Those things are
worth the frickin' fortune.
Heck yeah they are.
Bro, if you make this happen for me I will
strongly consider hanging out with you.
You serious bro?
Yep.
Two big buffalo's like
us out there in the wild.
We're in unisex, turquoise blouses.
Oh boy, that's going to cause a commotion.
The ladies aren't going to know what.
Listen, you get to keep the
hammer press under on you.
I'll make all your weird
family or dreams come true.
Two loose cannons.
We're in turquoise blouses.
Yep.
Let's do it.
And we've got $500.
$500 over here.
We've got $500 over here.
We've got $500.
We've got $600.
We've got $600 over here.
I'll give you $700.
We've got $700 over here.
We've got $800 over here.
We've got $850 over here.
$850 over here.
Do we hear any more?
Do we hear $900?
$900.
$900 is going once.
$900 is going twice.
And $900 is going three tops.
And so, to hometown hero, Garrett,
the garbage man, Garrison for $900.
I don't wanna cash that
for about six months.
What?
Yeah!
I'm the papa.
Cosmo's.
Whoo!
There!
Where is it?
I'm sorry, I didn't check the box.
Where will I hurry?
Hold on, Tor!
It does not mean you
should trash this unit!
I'm up against him, man.
I don't know.
My store.
I just...
I need a win, man.
I need... I need a win.
That's all I want.
This man has no respect
for the storage community.
Look, chugless was
not my first choice either,
but it was mom's dying
wish for us to live here.
Or at least that's how I interpreted it.
Yeah, I read something online.
This place sucks.
Anyways, rent is super low,
and I've got a full-time gig here,
so it's not really an offer where
we can turn down right now.
Yeah, I get it.
Look, I think you're
really gonna like it here.
Oh, what's going on with that, dude?
Oh my gosh, Henry, we're in Chugmas.
Stay high to tell me the chat.
All right, this is the new neighborhood.
When was this house built?
It's so nice to meet you.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
You knew bosses sent you this.
Oh, yeah.
People are working
at a potato chip factory.
Yeah, well, I'm running
their socials for a little
bit, said I'd get their
follower count past 75.
Nice!
You must be Henry.
Nice to meet you.
I'm done.
Right.
Why is there an alpaca
hang out of your car?
Well, real estate's not a lonely hustle.
I'll also do some mobile
zoo stuff on the side.
And who I gotta run, call
me if you need anything.
Also, really sorry about your mom.
It's really brave what you're doing.
I hope you know that.
Thank you.
Henry, breakfast is ready.
I'm coming.
Check it out.
I made you mom's signature
tater top breakfast pizza.
So you can hand out
slices on your first day?
I thought you wanted me to see normal.
I do.
What do you think I am?
I got you some body spray.
Signature scents are huge here.
Velvet mischief.
You're going to want to
spray it and then walk into it.
Don't be too direct.
It's really powerful.
Love you.
Love me too.
Smells like banana bread and food.
Your story's running cool.
Yeah, I know.
Looking for anything in particular.
Nah, I'm just checking some stuff out.
Non-committal, a classic loser mentality.
I can help.
I'm starting a mentorship program for
people who want to win at the game of life.
50 bucks an hour.
Cool.
They actually went at life.
That's literally the
answer I charge money for.
Tots.
Through the breakfast pizza.
My sister made up.
I'm supposed to hang outside
so that's cool to make friends.
Well, desperate for
day one, don't you think?
I also noticed that you're
wearing velvet mischief.
It's a wonderful cologne,
and I strongly believe that
every young man should
have his own signature scent.
I don't think I applied very much.
Listen, I'm gonna give
you a hot garbage tip.
Friendship is like a puzzle.
Sometimes you think you
need lots of pieces to be
cool, and sometimes it's
just one piece to be cool.
Then people will be
like, that's not a puzzle.
That's a picture.
And they have a right to speak to.
OK, well, I've got to go to school.
We're never nerd.
Just leave the pizza.
All right.
Let's put this name tag on.
Why does it have an exclamation point?
Oh, Henry, we're just
so thrilled to have you.
You're the first student
to enroll here ever since
that article came out
about the school rankings.
Anyway, I'm Vice Principal
Marlene and I'm an open book.
You probably heard that my husband
Clemente recently divorced me.
And to be honest, I expected
it to hurt more than it does.
You know, the fire went
out on our marriage 20
years ago, but we
stuck it out for the dogs.
Okay, let's get you to your first class.
Good morning!
Just a little something about myself.
I teach Jim, I teach her.
Financially, I'm living
in a nightmare, okay?
I wouldn't wish my life on my worst enemy.
Last year, I claimed
$4,000 on my tax return.
I also have several pending lawsuits, okay?
But most of my money is tied
up in a drone kiosk at the mall.
Okay, today we're gonna do a still life.
One orange?
One banana.
Let's get after it, people.
What is this?
13 over the still life is?
That means you just draw the thing.
Do the assignment next time.
That jetpack would never work.
It's kind of fool-per-factually.
It's just math.
My dad said math has been debunked.
Check it out.
New kid thinks he's a rocket scientist.
I'd love to be a rocket scientist.
So prove it.
Okay, so I know that we're all
very excited about the new rebrand,
but I don't think you should
call your party bags salt sacks
I was never here, OK?
Well, the good news is nobody died.
But the bad news is you've destroyed
the American potato to Pecanamy.
I'm sorry, OK?
It was an accident.
This could be grounds for expulsion, Henry.
I need you to call your guardian.
Hey, Mr.
Garbage Man, it's Henry.
The camp with the
Tateron top breakfast pizza.
Oh, yeah.
I have a weird favorite ask.
Could you come to my school
and pretend to be my uncle?
No way.
I don't do that stuff anymore.
I had 26 bucks.
I am Henry Zankle.
You?
The trash bag?
It's actually garbage, man.
Garbage, man, huh?
Oh, you can bag me up and
take me to the curb anytime.
But you got to bungee the lid,
because I got a lot of raccoons in there.
Whoever divorced you is a complete idiot.
It's don't get it.
It should have worked.
Not this rape, but it probably
just caused my sister her job.
Oh, wow.
You're super creative.
Guess I'm not the only
true talent and jugless.
Hey, uh, since you're going to
Juve, you mind if I get this flyer back.
People don't grow on trees and they're
really loud and the king goes anymore.
Well, you can have my book, too.
Because I'm done with it.
What's this stupid joke?
Who cares?
Plus a new age bullcrap.
I don't know what it does.
Hey, instructions.
Never under any circumstances
can bind the orb and crystal.
Do not fall this work even if you're a
struggling business owner and eat a ton of
cash fast because there's loads of pressure
down here, but it's not worth the danger.
I'm sorry.
I tried everything.
I didn't know what was to call.
No, it's okay.
What's going on?
Henry's missing.
I tried the school.
I tried to spawn a million times.
He's not answering.
He was supposed to be home hours ago.
I thought he's still being detention
for blowing up, checking the chip.
That was him.
Give me a call.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe this were here for one
day, and he's already the town villain.
Yeah, Adam.
He's fine.
He's just planning an abandoned mine shaft.
What?
I'm on.
I'll drive.
You can feed
Mr. Scribbles this plastic kid
if you want to keep
that pretty face of yours.
Happen.
OK. You go first.
I'll come here six.
Danger, whatever.
What are you doing down here?
He's my new mentor
Oh man, my bad!
We're not neither anymore.
I think this is Wyoming.
Wait, who are you again?
Garrett the garbage man, Garrison.
Game of the year, 1989.
Whatever.
I better think about it.
What the heck?
That's what I think it is.
It could be our first quest giver.
I'll do the talking.
All right!
Yeah!
Henry!
Come back here!
Lift it up, you fly.
You're running dangerous below on gold.
Don't let me be very clear.
You are all failures.
If you can't find more gold, I'll just send
you to the overworld to solve the size.
Find me more gold.
You.
What are you making?
Come closer.
It's all right.
Come on, I'm not going to bite you.
Ritchie!
Which hell will that
help me find more gold?
Oh!
What?
Well, looky what we have here.
Oh, time has come.
My leisure.
Was I unclear when I said no one?
Was to waste time on art or leisure?
The orb has returned.
It can't be.
Dennis?
You stole it from me and
now you will retrieve it.
It would be a privilege my leisure.
We're going to unbind you now.
Don't do anything stupid.
Of course, now, you can
trust this little dungeon, pup.
Let me just speak about it.
Go ahead, strike me down.
My piglins will make a
meal of your beautiful wolf.
How do I know you're telling the truth?
There's only one way to find out.
The orb for your little dog's life.
Ola, why is Quasquiver?
We humbly see gold.
Give us a quest that will
lead us to your treasure load.
Garbage, man.
I work in the animal field
and I am telling you that
thing doesn't understand
the word you're saying.
Shh.
We're talking.
Sorry about that.
What were you saying?
Come on, Henry.
We're going home.
Is that real quick to anyone else?
Alright everyone, stay
calm, rely on free garbage tip.
Fear is just weakness,
hijacking your body's cockpit.
What in the hell?
Henry!
Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry!
Cool.
Oh!
Who are you?
I am Steve.
Who are you people?
Where's Dennis?
Dennis, who's, we don't know any Dennis.
Then how'd you get that?
Hey, we're lying, we shot you.
It's my property.
Do you even know what that is?
It's the orb of dominance.
It's a cube.
OK. Ha ha!
You people seriously have no
idea what you're dealing with.
Hand it over and no one gets hurt.
No way.
OK, we need this thing to get home.
I hate to take a big fat dump of room
on your plans, but you can't get home.
Well, well, what do you
mean we can't get home?
Not without the Earth crystal.
You mean that little boxy thing?
Garbage man busted it!
Uh-uh.
Listen, Henry, why don't you hold this?
You got those good Frodo vibes, kid.
I got Frodo vibes.
Are you implying that we're stuck here?
Yes!
Unless you get the Earth
Crystal, it's your only way home.
There's only one way you
could ever replace it at the
Woodland Mansion, but going
there would get you all killed.
So it's staying here?
Fair enough.
Listen, I can get you home, but
then you gotta give me that orb.
So what are you going to do with it?
None of your attention!
So, what do you say?
Do we have a deal?
He did just kill like 20 zombies.
Well, I 15, but okay.
All right, Steve, under two conditions.
One, always address
me because I'm the leader.
Two, if you double
cross us, I will crack your
colossal with my butt
cheeks like a walnut.
This guy is such a toolbug.
I'm so sorry.
We just met this man,
and he's not the leader.
Well, it looks like Dr. Swalenstein
here just got himself a deal.
Oh, my gosh.
All right.
First, we need to load up on
some gear, or we're all going to die.
Let's go to mid-port village.
This guy's lost his mind.
Here it is!
Meat port village!
I got a secret stash of elite loot that'll
help us survive the woodland mansion.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, these guys!
Oh, these dudes?
They're the villagers!
They're total pacifists and vegetarians.
You don't bug them, they won't bug you.
They just like to chill, trade,
and eat buttloads of bread.
They love crushing a loaf.
So they built all this?
Yeah, most of it.
But the good stuff you see is all me.
Whoa.
See some kind of king?
No.
That's a legend.
Kid, anything you can dream
about here you can make.
Zero limits.
You know what I'm talking about.
That was your tower, right?
Yeah.
Pretty killer for a first build.
Relax.
It's just an iron goal.
I'm local security force.
But they're a bunch of big softies.
Unless you start messing with
the villagers, don't ever do that!
This place makes no sense.
Yo, I need protein-like ponto.
I got just the place, bro, Eman.
Oh, there.
Ho-hoo!
Oh, dude, I got goose
pimples just walking up on it.
You ever wonder what happens
when you mix hot lava and chicken?
I did, and you're about to find out.
You hear that?
That's the sound of sizzling.
Mm-hmm.
Smell that smell.
Mama, la la, cha cha cha cha.
Steve's lava-chicken, yes.
T.D.
is hell.
Ooh, mama, see tonight
you're ringing the bell.
Chris, Ben, Justin, now
you're having a snack.
Ooh, super spicy, it's a lava attack.
I have a small business, too.
The one thing I try to do is
not have my jingle suck butt.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Garbage man, you're a big time idiot.
What is it?
What?
General Chaga!
Hey Melgosha, what's going on?
Your old dungeon buddy,
Steve has betrayed us.
Well that's a bummer.
The orb is with four roundlings.
My spice tell me he has taken
them to his lava chicken check.
No way, I love that place.
La la la la la, cha cha cha cha.
You'll find us glorious bring me
that orb and kill the roundlings.
So like you want me to
end his life or whatever?
Are you serious?
What do you think I'm talking about?
Okay, I was just kind of
confused there for a second.
Take us me the woods so you don't zumbify.
Um, your majesty?
I don't think this is gonna
be enough to go around.
Gail with it.
No worries.
All right, drink up, guys.
You don't want to zomb a vibe
there, but just tiny steps, OK?
OK, so how do we find this
woodland mansion thing?
Over the mountains, into the dark forest,
right beyond the massive red shrooms.
Massive red shrooms.
Mm-hmm.
Big old red ones.
We need to find a real map, Steve.
This place is dangerous, and I
need to get my brother out of here.
Well, it seems like he's
having a pretty good time.
Look, your brother has a gift.
You know that, right?
You should let him explore it.
Creativity in this
world is key to survival.
Hey, well, in the real world,
things are a little bit different.
Creative kids get picked last for Jim.
They sit at the Bummer lunch
table, and they get bullied.
Don't I know it?
Do you even realize what he did back home?
He blew up chugging the chip.
Maybe I belong in this rock.
Henry, that's not what I meant.
It's not what I was saying at all.
Just so you know, I'm more of a
sister to Hank than you'll ever be.
Yeah.
Spick it.
You OK?
Fine.
Look, I found one of these
big-headed-looking doos that sells maps.
Looks legit.
Come on.
Welcome to the stash.
TNT, firework rocks.
It's also good for propulsion.
Boots of swiftness, diamond
armor, full set, and blades for days.
Everything will need to
make it to woodland mansion.
Whoa.
Boog's lab, bro.
Look, but don't touch.
Those are some of my favorite treasures.
What's this, junk?
That is an ender pearl.
Teleports you to wherever you throw it.
Yeah, right.
And that was the only one I had.
No, Biggie.
Almost died fighting an Enderman for it.
Come with me!
This is a crafting table.
Here's how it works.
You place these elements
in different patterns.
You got yourself a sweet blade.
You want to see a blade?
I'll show you a blade.
Yeah.
Heather.
Good!
That's OK, bud.
Buck cuts your useful here.
Yeah, they're cool, Garrett.
They're like nunchucks.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I made them.
They're buck chuckets.
Uh, they're what?
Hey, can I try something else?
Absolutely.
Bro, you had thoughts the whole time?
Yeah, sorry.
Ah!
It's a top launcher.
Dude, you just took boring junk from the
real world to create something amazing.
That is next level!
Hank, can I play with your
top launcher when you're done?
Yeah.
Sweet.
Hey, Steve.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Sure thing.
What's up?
You know that note you left with the orb?
You want them out the riches?
I read it.
Yeah.
There's riches everywhere.
Keep a fat stash of diamonds
at the redstone mines.
So this treasure load is on
the way to this mansion place.
Not really.
It's a major deed to or plus.
The mines can be perilous.
I'm gonna keep it simple for you, Steve.
He's smelling and stepping in.
Good day.
We need a map to the Woodland Mansion.
Oh, you see the map.
Nick, it's gone.
Someone's gone down.
Alright guys, just start
trashing their practice.
Villagers hate that.
I'm really sorry that I have
to annihilate you and stuff.
Now go should double cross me.
We just need that corn thingy.
You know this guy?
Yeah, we used to get
into some dungeon stuff.
He seems nice, but he's a cow.
Wow!
You look good, bro, hammer.
You lose some weight?
Stand back, Boris.
This pig is mine.
No.
I'm tired of getting all the glory.
This pig is mine.
Ninja Road.
Or what happened?
The danger putt, that's what happened.
Keep things new later.
We got to get to the ramparts.
Follow me!
Matt, we have to go now.
Don, I can't all leave him.
He's my entire family.
We need you.
I love.
OK, we'll meet him back
at the women's mansion.
We gotta go find him back.
Come on!
Garrett, what about Natalie?
We'll be here on the mansion.
Oh, whoa.
Oh, great.
Now what?
Ah!
Elytra wing suits.
Whoa!
Head for those maps!
I'd never heard you the one in Manchin!
Hey, don't talk about your elders!
Fight!
Move on!
Those things work, right?
Absolutely!
Jack it out!
I'm mine!
What is this?
Let me see you later.
I saw my graph three.
Wake for me.
Coming in.
Just relax.
Let my hips guide you if the only way.
For the channel!
We're not going to bed!
We're going to Chuggy!
We're going to have to go notice the toast!
Full man sandwich!
What the hell!
I'm not going to do that!
I'm ordering you to
make a full man sandwich!
Okay!
I'm gonna squeeze for your safety.
I understand.
Get out of here!
Get off me!
You can really fight Matt.
You can fight!
I have no idea where it came from.
There he is!
He's getting away!
I'm back here!
We did it back!
First we did a boat!
Okay, who got ya?
Okay, hurry!
You have guys flown away!
Nah, that's the worst boat I've ever seen.
I'm sorry, I have no idea what I'm doing.
Forget it!
Let's go!
Come on!
Oh, I am so sorry.
Oh my god.
Are you all right?
Your head is huge.
You're not gonna sue me, are you?
Because everyone wants to sue me once
I hit them with my Jeep Grand Cherokee.
Oh my.
How about this?
What if I just take you to dinner?
Would you like to go to dinner?
You got some talkin' to do, buddy.
Hank and I want some answers.
Like, how are we gonna stop those pigs?
And why some of my
peers are like gorgonzola?
Yeah, and who's that evil
source as you were talkin' about?
Look!
The sorceress is a pickling
queen called Nalgosha.
Those are her minions.
She ruled over them in a dark
hellscape called the Nether.
And I always keep a chunk of
gorgonzola in my front pocket, okay?
It's my best friend's favorite snaggy snag.
My best friend, Dennis.
Malgosha's path to villainy started
the way these things often do.
During the semi-finals
of the Nether Scott Talent.
Young Malgosha always dreamed
of being a world-class dancer.
Her moves were pretty out there.
No one in the Nether was ready for it.
It crushed her.
What I tell you about all that
dancing, you deserve to fail.
Creativity will never make you
happy, but you know what will?
Go!
Now go find some.
So from that day forward, she
denounced all forms of creativity.
If she ever gets that orb,
she'll block out the sun.
Netherward will flourish.
This beautiful world and
everything in it will wither and die.
And you were going to give it to her?
Great idea.
I'm not going to give it to her,
but I need that orb for leverage.
God, save Dennis.
Come.
Woodland mansion is just
beyond the redstone mountains.
We can go over or through.
Whatever's fastest.
through will be faster.
General Chungus, you had
failed me for the last time.
Yeah, I'm really sorry about that.
Bring out the beast.
What do you mean you
just have to put the bride in?
Well, he's as a victim.
Get it done.
Look, everybody knows
it wasn't my best day,
but I'm really trying
to set some new goals.
Make way for him.
There it is!
Kill him!
Wait, does this mean you're firing me?
Well done.
Now find the roundlings
and bring me the old!
We are so lost.
My one job was to
protect Henry and I blew it.
It just pops my mom and I
never let anything happen to him.
I guess I'm just not cut
out for this parenting stuff.
I wish I could have been a kid
for a little bit longer, you know?
It's not about feeling like I
could have done anything.
I hear you.
Being a grown-up sucks.
You got all these responsibilities,
and you just stop chasing your dream.
You think I like having 15 aussles?
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold up.
Let's just calm down.
I think this one just needs some TLC.
Yeah?
You like bones?
Oh, I bet you like bones.
Yes, you do.
That you do?
Yes.
Aren't you a beautiful one?
Yes, you are.
Did you learn?
I cannot believe you just did that.
What?
Dennis?
Steve's Dennis?
Uh-huh.
Okay, can you take us to him?
Oh.
Oh, Nat, I think this might be
our way to the Woodland Mansion.
Ah!
Let's follow that pooch.
Right, this way, gentlemen.
Ho-ho-ho!
Looky, looky here.
Welcome to the redstone mines.
You see that glowy stuff?
That's redstone.
The duck's energy.
He can build some
crazy contraptions with it.
I thought you said this was a diamond mine.
Easy big dog, they're here.
But be careful.
I said some booby traps a long time ago.
Can't find a life on me
remember where they are.
Here it is!
Thanks, Karen.
Thanks for diamonds.
That's what I'm talking about.
Steve delivers the goods.
Did you guys plan this?
I'm sorry, Henry.
Woo!
Yeah, I'm not.
What the heck, man?
Overlax.
No, he could be in the mansion already.
Thank you for it.
Oh no.
Never what?
What does that mean?
In February, sirs!
I built the kick-ass safer!
Just out the head!
Woo!
Dang it!
My torch blew out!
Why are we stopping?
We're a husky, low-gen, so I'm
gonna need a redstone-boosted bass.
What's that sound?
Crap!
My crepe or farm?
What are they in here?
It would breed me, sphin'!
We gotta get to the red storm rail!
You gotta sing this mess!
Get out of here, punch!
Okay.
We're not gonna make it!
Come on, come on!
Let's go!
Nice work, Gargard.
Your little detour almost got us killed.
Alive, you're so dramatic.
We're still alive.
What's your problem, man?
We didn't need those stupid diamonds.
I swear, you weren't literally the
most selfish person I ever met.
Whatever.
I need them.
Okay?
I need the diamonds, because I
need the money, because I'm broke.
You wouldn't know anything about that.
My life sucks, kid.
All right?
I'm a freaking loser.
There I said it.
I know it looks like I've
got it all put together, right?
I'm smart, funny, bilingual,
el humbly, to un-el fault out.
That's not the reality.
I'm not doing well.
I'm bad.
I'm washed up, Hank, and
I'm gonna lose everything.
And that's not the worst part.
I'm alone.
You're alone.
I was your friend.
Sorry about your finances.
The shop, Steve.
You know, I gotta tell you,
I'm having a great time.
I recently got divorced from
my husband Clemente, and the
main reason is, you know,
he didn't have any personality.
Not like you.
Are you finished?
No, I think he's Swedish.
But we're done with our meal.
There it is.
The woodland mansion.
We're going to get in there and get
the earth crystal and get you guys home.
Follow me.
Check this out.
Let's do this.
Pay close attention to Papa Steve.
The woodland mansion has three floors.
The first floor is loaded with vindicators.
Why is it dirt floor on the first floor?
I'm very confused.
I was trying to make three floors, but I
didn't have time to make, like, a dollhouse.
The second floor crawls with the focus.
They wield powerful dark magic.
This is the worst model I've ever seen.
Garrett, stop talking.
We're trying to figure out a plan.
How long have you been mad at me for?
I just got mad at you.
Please don't be mad at me for this, OK?
But I accidentally stole
the orb while you're crafting.
We cool now?
You are literally the worst
person in the entire world.
Guys, both of you eyes on my denim stretch.
Third floor, houses the light chamber.
That's where the earth crystal is.
But it's guarded by end of it.
Whatever you do, do
not let them in the eye.
The fry your brains out.
OK, well, I could build
stairs to the second floor,
sneaking through the window,
and snag the earth crystal.
That's a great idea, Hank.
But to pull it off, we're going to
need a pretty sweet diversion.
You know, look, we're cutting these guys.
It sounds crazy.
Hit me.
That's so hilarious.
That's a good day party.
Looks like it's everyone's birthday.
Get it.
To date is the best is to date you again.
Time for us to pull the bird.
Ahhh!
Gotta be kidding me.
You got this, gosh.
Reach down, dude.
You're the truckless kid, not love you.
Let's go on, Steve.
It's some kind of sadistic
vindicator fight club.
I've heard of these,
but I've never seen one.
You want me to fight the chicken?
It's a fight to the death, kid.
Chicken, jockey!
Ahh!
I'm sorry, little buddy.
Don't fall for a doctor!
That baby's got the heart of a demon!
No, you're not a demon, are you?
You're a cute little bugger face.
I'm just gonna...
This is all your fault, Jimmy.
That's the only thing we're going to do.
You saved my life.
That's what friends do, Garrett.
Hank, did you get the Earth Crystal?
Yeah, I got it.
Let's get out of this hellhole.
Where do you think you're going?
It's her!
You dabbies!
You really thought you
could defeat my great home!
News flash!
I built a new one!
Don't go, Chef!
Your reign is over!
You're wrong.
It's just beginning.
No!
Kill them!
We have work to do!
Goodbye, Steve!
Secret pigments.
They're going to blow this bridge sky high!
Sorry.
What?
Yeah!
Slant tube!
Come on, Derek.
Drop!
No, Steve.
Get him out of here.
Go ahead.
Save your sister and get home.
Derek, you don't have to view this.
No, get him home, Steve.
Tell my story and song.
Keep it metal.
Keep it heavy.
Real instruments.
Sats.
Mm-hmm.
Dennis?
Dennis!
Oh, boy, it's you.
It's really you.
Oh, my God.
How'd you find me?
He's one heck of a wolf.
He let us write to you guys.
Now understand why
you kept yourself so filthy
and smelly so Dennis
could find you one day.
Is he okay?
He's fine.
He's just resting.
Good.
It's a pretty rough crash landing.
Wait a minute.
Where are we?
You guys won't hate this?
No, we're not messing around.
We got the silk.
Don't look her!
What?
I was so afraid that I lost you.
I'm so afraid that I lost you, Duke.
I'm really sorry about Garrett.
With this rule, I'll talk in the overworld.
Never walk or spread like wildfire.
And all it's gold will be ours.
It has begun.
The Great Darkening!
Now Ghost is gathering all her forces.
She will destroy this land.
Unless we go get that orb.
What are we doing here?
Let's go fight some pigs.
I'm ready.
I'm done with those pigs.
Yeah, me too.
Let's do it for Godgar.
First we mine, then we craft.
Let's minecraft.
Mine.
One, two, three, two, nine, four.
What do you say?
Minecraft.
We should all say that on three.
What forget it?
There's no time.
Show us what you got, Henry.
OK. We've got a plan.
Killer recipes.
We're going to have to move fast.
Let's get to work.
First, we're gonna need Iron Angus.
Coming in a car.
Oh, yeah.
We're gonna need the
foods that's whipped in.
Time to light this place up.
We need a ton of diamonds.
It lays for days.
You want somebody?
We're ready.
Let's go save the overworld.
Listen up, my piddies.
Today, we take the
overworld, as ours, attack their
villages, burn their holes,
and there's a metrical fox.
All they have created, we destroy!
What are you standing around for?
Get out of here!
Go on!
Oh, no.
News flash, iron golems will
not attack unless provoked!
Real food, Travis!
No.
Ready?
Let's do this.
Oh, look at the sight!
Enjoying the show, are you?
Get down there and take care of the
Pulled jobs!
Okay, gosh.
Let's dance.
Bring it off!
My time is done!
I can't get that!
Chris!
I've got some for this!
It is!
Yeah!
You're alive!
Between us, I used
these water bucket tricks.
Pretty cool, huh?
Little bit.
Let's get this alarm going home.
All right, hey.
It's about about time.
Grab that stair.
I want you to jab in the tent.
Oh, yeah.
You failed which, the overworld lives on.
You too have fallen for the great lie.
You'll never be happy.
Dig down, you know, to hope,
to dream, to create, is to suffer.
You're right.
It is harder to create than to destroy.
That's why cowards
tend to choose the deuce.
Later, Gosh, every minute knowing
you has been a horror show waste of time.
Wait, one more thing.
Come close there.
Do you have a little knife that
you're going to try to stab me with?
No, I know.
I'm too late.
Come on.
Who's with the short?
Wait, wait.
Let me say one more thing.
Come close there.
No way.
No, really.
It's about you.
Fine.
Laying down here.
You really are the worst.
Goodbye.
This is it, really.
Come back.
I don't even have a noise.
Bill and I came back.
See you soon.
Hey!
You sure you want to go back Henry?
It won't feel like this.
There you got constraints,
judgements, obstacles.
Yeah, I know.
But I'm going to go make stuff anyway.
I like that.
You're a brave kid.
Steve, you still cool with this?
And if we... Yeah.
Of course, I still love you.
That's why I think this is a good idea.
You changed my life.
It's time for you to go change hers, too.
Earth?
Go now.
Dennis.
Change Dawn's life.
Go on a journey.
And think of me.
Dennis.
If I would've known you could sing like
that, it would help me get past your smell.
Garrett?
You are a truly bodacious warrior.
And a really good friend.
I wish you'd come home with us.
Thanks, cool.
But I don't have any friends.
My age.
You can make a great team.
But I'll come to you.
It needs to be my brother.
No, it doesn't.
Don't look at her.
It does.
No, it does not.
That does.
Love you guys!
Are you sure you don't want to come back?
Yeah, I'm staying here.
I got a bunch more stuff I want to build.
Why don't you bring some of
that magic to the real world?
Screw it.
I'm coming with.
Turns out the overworld taught us
you can create the life you dream of.
Even in the real world, Garrett's
store became the hottest place in town.
And the best part is new
friends were never far.
So with Henry and Natalie's help, we created
the hit game, Block City Battle Buddies.
All that time in the
overworld of everyone's game.
In every Friday, I would let it rip.
Yeah!
I used to wake up and
play back in my childhood.
They used to know that such a dirty shame.
They got my baby a chance
to let my imagination dance.
Hell, I came up with a different game.
Never have a lookin'
back cause I'll feel like this!
John finally got to
ditch a real estate job.
She and Dennis brought
the party wherever they went.
Natalie decided to share her
new skill set with the real world.
Survival mode, self-defense!
The streets are truckless
and never been safer.
You got them Natalie!
And Henry, he finally
got that jet back to work.
The rest don't know
the dry eye I feel the
hurtful With the power
of the world of sight
I know how much you look bred.
Marlene, your ex-husband's here.
He said it was an emergency.
Well, you tell him I've
got nothing to say to him.
You got to be kidding me, Marlene.
This is the guy.
Too late, Clemente.
You had your chance.
She's right, Clemente.
You totally blew it.
And now I read the rewards of your mistake.
You see, when Marlene's Jeep Grand
Cherokee ran me over, I was struck by
a love so powerful it transcended
the barriers of conventional speech.
Now I speak human and she speaks villager.
Marlene ever since we met last night,
I wanted to say, would you marry me?
Yes!
A thousand times!